VICTORIA HENDRICKS

PROFILE

Recent Software Engineer graduate with fundamental knowledge of software design, development, data analytics, and testing. Planning to take my 5 years of experience in healthcare into the world of technical development by utilizing my excelling programming and analytical skills to thrive as a software or data engineer.

EXPERIENCE

LEAD OPHTHALMIC TECHNICIAN, GEORGIA RETINA – 2019-PRESENT Acquired skills of management and problem-solving through running the clinic and troubleshooting all technical complications through our healthcare software and devices. Worked with Epic and Nextech Health Systems and devices from Optos, Zeiss, and Heidelberg.

CERTIFIED OPHTHALMIC ASSISTANT, GEORGIA RETINA – 2017-2019 Consisted of patient interaction, medical record documentation, billing/coding, assist to the physician in all medical procedures, and developed skills in using opto-coherent topography, angiography, and fundus photography.

MARKETING AND SALES REPRESENTATIVE, STARS AND STRIKES – 2011-2014 Worked with Microsoft Word, Excel, and Google Docs to create marketing documents and traveled to marketing events to present information and data information for the company.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPER CERTIFICATE, GEORGIA TECH – 2022

GRADUATE DEGREE IN PHYSIOLOGY, UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA – 2020

BACHELORS OF SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH FLORIDA – 2017

SKILLS

mySQL Sequelize Javascript. Node.js Express.js HTML CSS JSON

REFERENCES

Georgia Retina - EyeSouth Partners 678-317-0326

Aya Lewis - Lead Ophthalmic Technician 678-936-3631